autoeurope.com 2007-06-30

# Auto Europe Privacy Policy Description

**About Cookies**  
The Auto Europe web site does make limited use of cookies to better serve you. However, we do not store any personal or credit card information about you in these cookies. They do contain a session id number and some other basic information about your visit (for instance, which country you chose when you came to the site).

If you prefer, you can delete your Auto Europe cookies with our privacy tools listed on the right.

**Secure Transactions**  
All requests and credit card confirmations sent to us from our web site go through our secure server to protect your information. To verify that your browser is using the secure server, look for a small padlock icon on the lower part of your browser window. If it is shown in the 'locked' position, your transaction is secure. (Please note, the security features are only turned on for pages where you can view and submit your request or confirm your quote by providing your credit card number.)

**Email Newsletter**  
We use an 'opt-in' email newsletter. This means you will be sent a confirmation email when your address is submitted to us. If you do not respond to this message, we will not send you any more email. You can also unsubscribe from our email newsletter or modify the format in which you receive it at any time.

**About Your Email Address and Personal Information**  
Auto Europe recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this site. We will be asking from you the following information, depending on what specific service you require from us: name, e-mail address, home address, phone number, gender, date of birth, city and country of birth, driving license number, class of driving license, country of issue of driving license, passport number and type, and country of issue of passport. We will only use this information to contact you regarding any requests or bookings made with us and to process your request for booking, and we will only send you our email newsletter if you choose to opt-in to it. Otherwise you will not receive any unsolicited email from us. In addition, we may selectively provide certain information to other companies or organizations that have products or services we think may interest you. If you do not want to receive promotional materials regarding third party products or services, and you indicate this preference when you provide your personal information to us, we will honor your preference by not providing your information to such third parties. If you have chosen to allow us to provide your information to others, you may use the privacy tools on the right to opt-out at anytime. Please note that in order to process your request or booking, we may have to share your personal data with our suppliers.

If you have registered to be a member of our site and have logged into our site, your personal information will be retrieved whenever you send in a request or choose to edit your member information. If you share your computer with others, please make sure you log out when you are done using our site to avoid inadvertantly giving others access to your account. 

You may at any time, request to see the information which is being held by us on you and request to make amendments to this information or delete this information. Please contact us at [privacy-manager@autoeurope.com](mailto:privacy-manager@autoeurope.com).

Please note that this site is operated on servers controlled by Auto Europe, LLC, a US based company, and that any data which you will to us will be processed not only by Auto Europe Ltd but also by Auto Europe, LLC, in the United States. If you do not want your data to be transferred to Auto Europe, LLC, in the United States, please do not use this site. By using our services, you acknowledge that your data will be processed in the United States and recognize that the transfer of your data to the United States to Auto Europe, LLC is required for us to provide you with our services.

**Affiliates**  
If you have communicated with one of our affiliates with respect to your request or booking, you will have been informed that those services are provided by us and you agree and recognize that personal data which you will have provided to our affiliates will be used by us in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Prohibited Uses**  
It is prohibited to use any device, software or routine, directly or indirectly, to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of this web site, any activity being conducted on this site or to place any undo load or stress upon our systems. We monitor access to the site for data scrapers and automated access of information and we will block processes engaging in these activities.

|  |  **Privacy Tools**  
---  
**Delete Cookies**  
This will remove the Auto Europe cookies from your web browser. If have not yet sent in your request to us, please do so before clicking this link or you will need to rebuild your request. 

* * *

**Email Unsubscribe**  
This will bring you to a form that will allow you to unsubscribe from our email travel newsletter. 

* * *

**Email Modify**  
If you are having trouble reading our email travel newsletter, this will allow you to have all future versions sent to you in a text-only format. 

* * *

**Opt-In/Opt-Out**  
You can use this form to specify whether we may share your personal information with others. 

* * *

**Web Site Terms & Conditions**
